Guide to the School of Architecture, Yale University, Records Concerning Events and Exhibitions
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Year-end student work exhibits [computer files], 2006-2009; Accession 2009-A-212; 10,957 megabytes (Box 1–3)
  - Well Done: 2006-2007 Year-End Exhibit of Student Work, 2007 May 18 - June 1
    - Advanced Graduate Section
      - Elisa Lui; Master of Architecture I, computer file (AI), 2007
      - Mako Maeno; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Jeff McBride; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Rustam-Marc Mehta; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Thomas Moran; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Seung Hwan Namgoong; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Clinton Prior; Master of Architecture I, computer file (PostScript), 2007
      - Dryden Razook; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (JPEG)
      - Reidel, Jacob; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (TIFF)
      - Jeffrey Richards; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Sam Roche; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PostScript)
      - Neil Sondgeroth; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PSB)
      - Ayumi Sugiyama; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (INDD)
      - Jean Suh; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Adrienne Swiatocha; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - James Tate; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Audrey Vuong; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Weston Walker; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - William West; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Xinghua Zhao; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (JPEG)
      - Mohammed Balila; Master of Architecture II, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Katherine Corsico; Master of Architecture II, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Jason deBoer; Master of Architecture II, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Ayat Fadaifard; Master of Architecture II, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Soo-Hyun Kim; Master of Architecture II, 2007; computer file (JPEG)
      - Yoo Jung Lee; Master of Architecture II, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Karl Mascarenhas; Master of Architecture II, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Carol Ann Ruiz; Master of Architecture II, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Joe Smith; Master of Architecture II, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Julia Suh; Master of Architecture II, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Enrique Ramirez; Master of Environmental Design, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Molly Steenson; Master of Environmental Design, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Federica Vannucchi; Master of Environmental Design, 2007; computer file (JPEG)
    - H.I. Feldman Prize Section, 2007
      - Jeff Richards + Seung Hwan Namgoong, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Serra Kiziltan + Neil Sondgeroth, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Allen Slamic, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Xinghua Zhao, 2007; computer file (TIFF)
      - Dana Getman, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Sini Kamppari, Neil Sondgeroth + Aaron Taylor, computer file (AI), 2007
      - William West, 2007; computer file (PDF)
  - A to Z: Year-End Exhibit of Student Work 2007-2008, 2008 May 23 - August 22
    - Advanced Graduate Section
      - Claire Axley; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Elizabeth Baldwin; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Moises Berrun; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Tom Bosschaert; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Gene Cartwright; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Ji-eun Cha; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Jamie Chan; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Jonathon Cielo; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Minna Colakis; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Christopher Corbett; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Michael Crockett; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Charles DiNatale; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Jennifer Dubon; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Todd Fenton; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Garret Gantner; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Marc Guberman; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Gabrielle Ho; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Mark Hoffman; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Alan Knox; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Ireta Kraal; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Whitney Kraus; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Michael Krop; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Brent Martin; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Nicholas McDermott; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Elizabeth McDonald; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Maria Melniciuc; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Shaghayegh Meshkinpour; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Lydia Miller; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Sara Murado-Arias; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Hojin Nam; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Marc Newman; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Stephen Nielson; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Nobuki Ogasahara; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Garrett Omoto; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Jason Pytko; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Nathan Rich; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - David Riedel; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Christopher Rubino; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Jeong Yeon Ryoo; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Dylan Sauer; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Erica Schroeder; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Benjamin Smoot; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Leo Stevens; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Isaac Strackbein; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Kathryn Stutts; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Chiew Hong Tan; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Quang Truong; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Mark Van Brocklin; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Christina Wu; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Alberto Zamora; Master of Architecture I, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Ashima Chitre; Master of Architecture II, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Santiago del Hierro Kennedy; Master of Architecture II, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Kyung Sook Kim; Master of Architecture II, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Lorenzo Marasso; Master of Architecture II, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Amrit Pilo; Master of Architecture II, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Michael Powers; Master of Architecture II, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Maryjane Starks; Master of Architecture II, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Andrew Steffen; Master of Architecture II, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Aaron Taylor; Master of Architecture II, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Elizabeth Bishop; Masters of Environmental Design, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Kathleen John-Adler; Masters of Environmental Design, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Zachary White; Masters of Environmental Design, 2008; computer file (PDF)
    - H.I. Feldman Prize Section, 2008
      - Gemma (Kyung Sook) Kim, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Aaron Taylor, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Alan Knox, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Dylan Sauer + Ben Smoot, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Chiew Hong Tan, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Marc Guberman, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Bo Crockett, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Yichen Lu, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Mary Jane Starks, 2008; computer file (PDF)
      - Dylan Sauer, 2008; computer file (PDF)
- School of Architecture exhibits [computer files], 2008-2009; Accession 2010-A-016; 4540 (Box 1–5)
  - David Schwarz Internship and Traveling Fellowship: Alexandra Burr; George Nelson Scholarship: Garret Gantner; Digital Media: student work from various studios and classes using the YSOA Digital Media Fabrication equipment, curated by John Eberhart, faculty, 2008 March 1 - June 1; 26; 26 computer files (TIFF)
  - Rome Project: Stephen Harby and Alec Purves, faculty, 2008 September 1 - October 24; 10
    Participating students of the Rome 2008 Program created the exhibit. In this program, selected students travel to Rome, Italy, under the direction of faculty Alexander Purves and Stephen Harby.
  - Building Project: Adam Hopfner, faculty; Systems Integration: Martin Finio, faculty, 2008 October 27 - December 12; 33 computer files (TIFF)
  - Shaping Perception: Graduate Drawing Coursework; Sophia Gruzdyz, Dino Marcantonio, and Paloma Pajares, faculty, 2009 January 12 - March 6; 25 computer files (TIFF)
    Work from the graduate drawing seminars: 802A Geometry, Drawing and Visual Inquiry; 803A Drawing and Architectural form; 811B Classical Drawing.
  - Worlds Away: New Suburban Landscapes, 2009 March 2 - May 10; 17 computer files (TIFF)
    This exhibit was organized by the Walker Art Center, Minneapolis, in association with the Heinz Architectural Center at the Carnegie Museum of Art, Pittsburgh.
- Films for exhibitions, 2010; Accession 2010-A-072; 617.8
  - Film for the exhibition "What We Learned: The Yale Las Vegas Studio and the Work of Venturi Scott Brown & Associates", 2010; 7; computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 1U)
  - Film loop for "In Retrospect: Scully, Roche and Pelli Discuss Morse and Stiles Colleges at Yale", 2010; 7
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 2U)
- School of Architecture exhibits [computer files], 2008-2010; Accession 2010-A-090; 5198.62
  - Shaping Perception: Graduate Drawing Coursework seminar, 2008 January - March 7; 20
    General
    Seminars conducted under faculty direction of Sophia Gruzdys, Dino Marcantonio, Paloma Pajares, Kent Bloomer, Turner Brooks, and Phil Grausman.
  - Student scholarship work exhibition, 2009 March 16 - August 1; 50
    Includes: Amy Chang for the David Schwarz Internship and Traveling Fellowship; Jack Brough and Parsa Khalili for the George Nelson Scholarship; and Isaiah King for the Takenaka Internship.
  - No Time Like the Present: Year End Exhibition of Student Work 2008-2009, 2009 May 22 - August 7; 21
  - The Green House: New Directions in Sustainable Architecture and Design, 2009 August 24 - October 16; 20
    Organized by the National Building Museum in Washington, D.C.
  - Student scholarship works exhibition, 2010 March 22 - July 30; 39
    Includes: Carmel Bonfigli for the David Schwarz Internship and Traveling Fellowship; Palmyra Geraki and Aidan Doyle for the George Nelson Scholarship; and Carlos Felix Raspall Galli for the Takenaka Internship.
- Photographs of Master of Architecture thesis juries, Spring 1965; Accession 2010-A-098
  - Black and white photographs, 1965 (Box 1)
    - Digital copies, 23
  - Computer files (Box 2)
- Exhibit programs and photographs of exhibit installations, 2011-2012; Accession 2013-A-018
  - "Ceci n'est pas une reverie: The Architecture of Stanley Tigerman", 2011 August 22-November 4 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Gwathmey Siegel: Inspiration and Transformation", 2011 November 14-2012 January 28 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "Massimo Scolari: The Representation of Architecture, 1967-2012", 2012 February 6-May 4 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "Big Plans: Year-End Exhibition of Student Work", 2012 May 19-July 28 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Exhibit programs, catalogs and event memorabilia, 1998, 2012-2013; Accession 2013-A-066
  - Exhibit catalog, "Architecture in Dialogue, the Peter Eisenman Collection at Yale", 2012 October (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Exhibit programs, "Sounds of Architecture", 2012 October (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Exhibit program, "Le Mani di Caravaggio" by Barry Svigals (Yale '76), 2012 November (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Exhibit program, "Women in Architecture", 2012 November-December (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Exhibit and event memorabilia, "George Nelson: Design for Living", 2012 November-2013 February (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Exhibit program, "Achtung Berlin", 2013 February (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Poster, "Yale School of Architecture Class of 1972 40th Reunion", 2012 May (Box 2)
  - Exhibit poster, "Masters of Environmental Design: A Critical Analysis", 1998 February (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Poster, "Convening Yale: A Series of Conversations with Yale Scholars: Dean Robert A.M. Stern, Yale School of Architecture", 2012 October (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Poster, "YSOA Movie Night", Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Exhibit programs and photographs of exhibit installations, 2012-2014; Accession 2015-A-026
  - "Palladio Virtuel" by Peter Eisenmann with Matt Roman, 2012 August 20-October 27 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "George Nelson: Architect, Writer, Designer, Teacher", 2012 November 8-2013 January 26 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "White Cube, Green Maze: New Art Landscapes", 2013 February 14-May 4 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Year-End Exhibition of Student Work", 2013 May 19-July 27 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "Everything Loose Will Land" by Sylvia Lavin, 2013 August 28-November 9 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "Stage Designs" by Ming Cho Lee, 2013 November 20-2014 February 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "Archaeology of the Digital", 2014 February 20-May 3 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "Year-End Exhibition of Student Work", 2014 May 18-July 26 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Posters for events and open houses, 2007-2015; Accession 2016-A-041; 3
  - Lectures, symposia, and exhibitions posters for spring semesters, 2008-2015 (Folder 1)
  - November open house posters, 2007-2015 (Folder 1)
  - Poster for re-dedication of Paul Rudolph Hall and dedication of Jeffrey H. Loria Center for the History of Art and Robert B. Haas Family Arts Library, 2008 (Folder 1)
- Posters for events, lectures, and open houses, 2016-2017; Accession 2017-A-043
  This accession consists of posters for School of Architecture Fall 2016 events and lectures, the fall symposium "Aesthetic Activism," fall open house, and Spring 2017 events and lectures.
  - Posters, 2016-2017 (Folder 1)